Hallelujah!
Viewers, thank you for your time.
God's time is the best.
I want to rejoice with you because the atmosphere is of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
All you need is to meditate on the testimonies you have been hearing since morning.
A lot of testimonies, that is God's work.
Meditate on the Word.
The more you meditate on the Word, the more your spirit - heart - acts upon the Word.
When the Word dominates our heart, it influences our character and our conduct.
The testimony of this, the testimony of that - they all point to salvation.
The more you meditate on the Word - testimonies - the more your heart acts upon the Word.
And when we allow all these to influence us, it leads to good character and conduct.
When all what you have been seeing since morning, hearing since morning,
the message the evangelist delivered here today...
If you allow all these to dominate your heart, it will influence your conduct and your character.
When you leave here today, you will just find yourself behaving in a different way.
No longer the way you were behaving before.
You are a smoker, you find yourself no longer smoking.
You talk too much, you just find yourself....
We are all waiting for something.
When healing, anointing is present, we put a demand through our faith.
But there is healing, anointing everywhere.
This is why you can dance, you are happy since morning.
Those who have diabetes, they can't feel it any longer.
Hypertension is suddenly gone.
You have been dancing, these are the things you cannot do at home without taking a drug or tablet.
But you have been...
There is something!
There is something ... what is that something?
Oh, my God.
For you to suddenly have that faith that there is something you cannot see.
You have not seen, you don't know that something but because of your faith,
you believe there is something!
That is faith.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Faith is expecting God to do what He promised to do.
That is faith!
I saw you when you were going round.
There is something..
When you look, you can't see that something.
There is something. What is that; where is that something?
And yet you have not seen that something - because you believe!
Faith, that is faith.
So, here we have healing anointing.
I can feel it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So, when healing anointing, I mean healing virtues, is present in a place -
through our faith, we put a demand on the anointing.
Miracles and all of God's blessings come by putting a demand on the anointing through our faith.
The anointing is everywhere; it is more than sufficient.
So what you are demanding - it is more than enough.
Faith is a trust. Say it to your neighbour.
Faith is a trust.
I can't hear you.
Again.
Faith is a trust.
This is why you need that trust - faith to put a demand on the anointing.
Anointing is the power of God.
Where there is God, there is power
Here God, here power.
When God smiles, power smiles.
When God walks, power walks.
When God sits, power sits.
When God looks, power looks.
So, power of God.
Without that faith, you cannot put a demand -
demand for healing, blessing, deliverance, salvation.
Just mention those things you demand for.
You can now put a demand on what? On anointing; the power of God.
There is no other means.
this is why the Bible says: Only faith pleases Him.
Only faith pleases him.
[Song: Trust and Obey]
Only faith pleases Him. Nothing else!
And there is so much stress when you talk of faith.
People begin to say, "Ah faith ...ah faith, I don't have faith". No no no!
No, faith is not something you look within.
It is simple. Just grab it this way.
When you realise that God is reliable, like many testimonies you heard today
and you are able to consult, meet them to ask them what are you saying
and you are able to establish your facts
and you realise that truly, what they are saying is true -
then, God is reliable.
And the moment you realise that God is reliable, faith grows simultaneously.
Like as you are sitting down.
Begin to meditate over what you have seen today.
Meditate on the message.
Begin to meditate, meditate, meditate.
And the more you meditate, the more your spirit - heart - acts upon the Word.
Begin to meditate in your heart.
Whatever you receive now, without maintenance, it is useless.
It's better not to ask for something you cannot maintain.
It's better not to receive something you cannot maintain
because it will expose you and put you in the hands of the enemy.
Those who know you to be this, suddenly later realise that you are zero.
They will make mockery of you.
It takes faith to maintain your position to the end.
The beauty of our achievement is when we no longer live and the achievement is still there.
Tell your neighbor: The beauty of our achievement, the glory of our achievement
is when we are no longer living but that achievement is still there,
lingering on in the eyes and ears of children yet unborn.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That is the beauty.
We are not necessarily being blessed by God because of today
but we are blessed because of tomorrow,
when we are no longer living.
Children yet unborn want to see things that can influence them to do right.
They say, "Ah, I want to be this... Ah, I want to be this".
"This person with such name lived such kind of life."
"This is what to achieve." - "No, no, I would love to be like him!"
It's not necessarily because of today you are blessed.
You are blessed because of tomorrow when you are no longer living
but that achievement continues to live
so that our children yet unborn can be influenced in a positive way by our achievement
because you will no longer live to educate them, to tell them the right way to follow.
But what you have achieved will be the one to talk to them, to tell them what to do.
Your concentration is so much on what you want to achieve - what you need.
That is your concentration.
Yes, you want to be this, you want to be that!
Vanity upon vanity.
We have so many role models - the good and the bad - in our family and community.
You have seen so many that are poor, that are suffering throughout their lives
and seen so many achieve great things.
You have seen so many that are living and those that are no longer living.
Which part are we following?
If you are known today and you are not known tomorrow, what is the value of it?
If your name is written today and your name vanishes tomorrow, what is the value?
Please, brethren, think about tomorrow.
Don't be deceived by the little you have.
Are you talking of marriage?
If you are thinking of the future - tomorrow - you would not rush.
You would not get married just like that without asking God
if this marriage will stand for tomorrow.
Many marriages will stand for today, but will not be able to stand for tomorrow.
Many businesses will stand today but will not be able to stand tommorow.
Many relationships will stand today but will not be able to stand tommorow.
But we should look for the One that will stand tomorrow because today is yours; tomorrow - God's.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Back to faith.
[MESSAGE TITLE:] FAITH IS MAINTENANCE
You will maintain your life when you live a life of faith.
You will be able to maintain your business, finances and health.
But to maintain this deliverance or whatever you receive from God - without faith, it is not possible.
That is why Jesus said, "I will make you fishers of men...fishers of men....fishers of men".
If you follow Him.
You can only follow Him by faith.
Now, let's define faith.
When faith comes, it influences our conduct and character.
Yes.
How does this faith come?
Let's think about it.
Because you read the Bible, if I now take you to the message in the Bible that says,
"Faith comes by hearing the Word of God and obey",
you will say, "Ah, I have been hearing, I have been obeying, what else again?"
I will not take you to that.
Let me take you in a very short way.
Because the one we are used to "Faith comes by hearing and hearing the Word of God" -
may be difficult for you.
Let me just take you in a short way.
I was talking of meditation.
Meditation is a thing of the heart.
Since you know that faith lives in your heart, start it now.
Begin to meditate.
Meditate what I'm saying,
what you have been seeing since morning,
the testimony of people.
i will not use the word 'think'.
I will leave the word 'think' for your situation.
We think about our situation.
What am I going to eat today?
How will I pay the money? The debt?
How will I get out of this mess?
How will I pay my house rent? That is 'think'.
I will leave the word 'think' for your situation.
The word 'meditation' is a visit to God.
Meditation comes from the heart.
Thinking, many times, comes from mental assent.
The more you meditate on them, on those things,
the more your spirit - heart - acts, agrees, joins.
It is our heart now that we need to work on.
Whatever you engage your heart with influences your character and conduct.
Whatever your heart engages on would influence your character and conduct.
Now, engage your heart over what you have seen today, the testimony of people,
the message you heard from the evangelist, when you watch emmanuel tv.
All what you are seeing, the message, the testimony - engage your heart.
Not thinking - engage your heart.
When you engage your heart, what you are seeing or hearing on Emmanuel TV
will begin to influence your conduct and character.
That is faith.